ob.tc 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Respecting users’ privacy is important to DesignRush LLC (“DesignRush” or “We,” “Us,” or “Our”). Read this section to learn about personal information that we collect and how it may be used.  By entering this website (the “site”), you agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, including any use of cookies by us.  Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future visits.  If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to use or access the site in any manner.

**A.     LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES**  
Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy and information collection practices.

**B.     PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION AND USE**  
We only collect personally identifiable information that is submitted to us via the site.  Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity.  This may include, but is not limited to: your name or business entity, title with the applicable business entity, personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or cellular telephone numbers, fax number, industry sector, and/or any other information requested on the applicable form.  

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information from anyone who visits the site.  Such information may include the type of device you are using and its location, the browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider.  We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the site, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, and to analyze site usage.  This information may also be transmitted to a third party analytics provider for our use only.

**C.     DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that an applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user.

**D.     COOKIES**  
This Site may use cookies from time to time to improve the performance of this site and enhance your browsing experience.  By continuing to use the site, you consent to our use of cookies.  You may manage your cookies preferences, including disabling and/or deleting cookies, through your browser settings.  However, please note that disabling cookies may limit your browsing enjoyment on this site.  What are cookies?: Cookies are small text files that a website sends to your computer, laptop, tablet, or smartphone where they are stored in order to save and track data about your use of the website.  The next time you visit the same website, cookies allow the website to identify you.  Cookies allow us to track your browsing history, to adjust the website to your preferences, and present you with content and offers tailored to your interests. 

**D.     UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**  
From time to time we may change our Privacy Policy and practices and will post an updated copy on the site.  All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the site. Please check this page for updates.  We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy as required by law. 

**E.     CONTACT US**  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: [info@designrush.com](mailto:info@designrush.com).

© 2018 DesignRush LLC
